<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thomas Maintenance</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Thomas Maintenance</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 12:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We provide a wide range of Janitorial Services...</title><link>/services/intro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>/services/intro/</guid><description>Power washing Professional Carpet Cleaning Window Cleaning Commercial Floor Scrubbing/Buffing Recycling Bin Services  We will maintain your recycling areas and ensure that all recycling and organics bins are placed at curbside on pick up days.</description></item><item><title>Working with your Property Management Company</title><link>/services/second/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate><guid>/services/second/</guid><description>Over the years we have built up a fine reputation with a number of property management companies. The workload for Property Managers is always high, therefore it is important that we continue to be an efficient janitorial service.
We carry liability Insurance and we are registered with the Worker&amp;rsquo;s Compensation Board of B.C. We have completed the WCB - Workplace Hazardous Materials Information System (WHMIS) course to ensure safe usage and storage of all cleaning compounds used on premises.</description></item><item><title>Quality Control</title><link>/services/third/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>/services/third/</guid><description>To ensure that a high standard of cleanliness is maintained, all buildings are inspected regularly as to meet or exceed the standard set out by the client.
What is WHMIS? Workplace Hazardous Materials Information System. We ensure safe usage and storage of all cleaning compounds used on premises. We are registered with the Worker&amp;rsquo;s Compensation Board of B.C. For any further information concerning our WCB coverage and insurance please email us.</description></item><item><title>A message to our clients and property managers</title><link>/notice/notice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 12:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/notice/notice/</guid><description>Please be assured that our janitors are putting forth an earnest effort to diligently disinfect all common door handles, exit door push bars, elevator panels and all other surfaces where people can touch. Please stay safe.</description></item><item><title>About Thomas Maintenance</title><link>/about/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>/about/about/</guid><description>Since 1990 our guarantee to our clients has been to provide a professional efficient janitorial service. A keen attention to detail is important.
We Value Communication Communication is an integral part of any successful business. We pride ourselves on our efficiency to stay in close contact with Property Managers and to act quickly in carrying out their instructions. Occasionally a concern can arise which will call for an immediate response from our maintenance team.</description></item><item><title>What Others are saying...</title><link>/recommend/recommend1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>/recommend/recommend1/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;We have enjoyed working with TMi since 1990. Always pleased with their team&amp;rsquo;s attention to detail and excellent communication.&amp;rdquo; Bunny Porteous, Senior Property Manager First Services Residential “Highly Recommend your firm for going the extra mile. Great Staff” Liz Der, Operations Coordinator Gammon International
TMi has been steady and reliable for many years comparing with other janitorial contractors we came across in the past years … Andrew Hui, Property Manager Dorset Realty of Canada Ltd &amp;ldquo;The best thing about the team from Thomas Maintenance was the peace of mind they gave us.</description></item></channel></rss>