<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thomas Maintenance</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Thomas Maintenance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We provide a wide range of Janitorial Services...</title>
      <link>/services/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/intro/</guid>
      <description> Power washing Professional Carpet Cleaning Window Cleaning Lighting and balast replacement </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recycling and Organics Bin Services</title>
      <link>/services/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/second/</guid>
      <description>We will maintain your recycling area and ensure that all recycling bins are placed at curbside on pick up days. Contact us for a quote for this service.
Professional Look For security reasons while on site we wear a uniform bearing the Thomas Maintenance Logo. This lends to a professional look and at the same time identifies us as maintenance personal. Picture identification tags can be worn if requested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality Control</title>
      <link>/services/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/third/</guid>
      <description>To ensure that a high standard of cleanliness is maintained, all buildings are inspected regularly as to meet or exceed the standard set out by the client.
What is WHMIS? Workplace Hazardous Materials Information System. We ensure safe usage and storage of all cleaning compounds used on premises. We are registered with the Worker&amp;rsquo;s Compensation Board of B.C. For any further information concerning our WCB coverage and insurance please contact us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Thomas Maintenance</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Our guarantee to our clients is to provide a professional efficient janitorial service. To be successful in this highly competitive business requires a keen attention to detail. Therefore we are continually aware of the interests of the condominium owner and we show this by working hard at maintaining a high standard of cleanliness through out all common areas. Why? Because these areas are extensions of your home or business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>