<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Thomas Maintenance</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Thomas Maintenance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We provide a wide range of Janitorial Services...</title>
      <link>/services/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/intro/</guid>
      <description>Power washing Professional Carpet Cleaning Window Cleaning Commercial Floor Scrubbing/Buffing Recycling Bin Services We will maintain your recycling areas and ensure that all recycling and organics bins are placed at curbside on pick up days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with your Property Management Company</title>
      <link>/services/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/second/</guid>
      <description>Over the years we have built up a fine reputation with a number of property management companies. With recent changes to the Strata Property Act, the workload for Property Managers has greatly increased. Therefore it is important that we continue to be an efficient janitorial service.
Our company has in place liability Insurance. We are registered with the Worker&amp;rsquo;s Compensation Board of B.C. We have completed the WCB - Workplace Hazardous Materials Information System (WHMIS) course to ensure safe usage and storage of all cleaning compounds used on premises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality Control</title>
      <link>/services/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/third/</guid>
      <description>To ensure that a high standard of cleanliness is maintained, all buildings are inspected regularly as to meet or exceed the standard set out by the client.
What is WHMIS? Workplace Hazardous Materials Information System. We ensure safe usage and storage of all cleaning compounds used on premises. We are registered with the Worker&amp;rsquo;s Compensation Board of B.C. For any further information concerning our WCB coverage and insurance please email us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>